<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CoronavirusTrackerApp</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading</string>
    <string name="network_not_available">Network not available</string>
    <string name="how_it_spreads">Coronavirus disease spreads primarily through contact with an infected person when they cough or sneeze. It also spreads when a person touches a surface or object that has the virus on it, then touches their eyes, nose, or mouth.</string>
    <string name="symptoms">People may be sick with the virus for 1 to 14 days before developing symptoms. The most common symptoms of coronavirus disease (COVID-19) are fever, tiredness, and dry cough. Most people (about 80%) recover from the disease without needing special treatment.</string>
    <string name="do_s">1. Wash your hands regularly for 20 seconds, with soap and water or alcohol-based hand rub.
        \n2. Cover your nose and mouth with a disposable tissue or flexed elbow when you cough or sneeze.
        \n3. Avoid close contact (1 meter or 3 feet) with people who are unwell.
        \n4. Stay home and self-isolate from others in the household if you feel unwell.
</string>
    <string name="dont_s">1. Touch your eyes, nose, or mouth if your hands are not clean</string>
    <string name="open_drawer">Open Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_drawer">Close Drawer</string>
    <string name="treatments">Self-care
        \n1. There is no specific medicine to prevent or treat coronavirus disease (COVID-19). People may need supportive care to help them breathe.
        \n2. If you have mild symptoms, stay at home until you’ve recovered.
        \n3. You can relieve your symptoms if you:
            \n - rest and sleep
            \n - keep warm
            \n - drink plenty of liquids
            \n - use a room humidifier or take a hot shower to help ease a sore throat and cough
    \4. Medical treatments
    \n If you develop a fever, cough, and have difficulty breathing, promptly seek medical care. Call in advance and tell your health provider of any recent travel or recent contact with travelers.</string>

    //Names of Indian States
    <string name="delhi">Delhi</string>
    <string name="andaman">Andaman and Nicobar Islands</string>
    <string name="andhra">Andhra Pradesh</string>
    <string name="bihar">Bihar</string>
    <string name="chandigarh">Chandigarh</string>
    <string name="chhattisgarh">Chhattisgarh</string>
    <string name="goa">Goa</string>
    <string name="gujarat">Gujarat</string>
    <string name="haryana">Haryana</string>
    <string name="himachal">Himachal Pradesh</string>
    <string name="jammu">Jammu and Kashmir</string>
    <string name="karnataka">Karnataka</string>
    <string name="kerala">Kerala</string>
    <string name="ladakh">Ladakh</string>
    <string name="mp">Madhya Pradesh</string>
    <string name="maharashtra">Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="manipur">Manipur</string>
    <string name="mizoram">Mizoram</string>
    <string name="odisha">Odisha</string>
    <string name="puducherry">Puducherry</string>
    <string name="punjab">Punjab</string>
    <string name="rajasthan">Rajasthan</string>
    <string name="tamilnadu">Tamil Nadu</string>
    <string name="telangana">Telengana</string>
    <string name="uttarakhand">Uttarakhand</string>
    <string name="up">Uttar Pradesh</string>
    <string name="wb">West Bengal</string>
    <string name="alert_dialog_ok_label">ok</string>

    <style name="loading">Loading</style>
</resources>
